In select,
I would like to know from you that
you have recently given your health insurance
that you have leaked all over the internet, so
how was your experience with the plane, the
experience of change in the hospital, so if you
call your claim settlement special episode 2 part my spirit, then a
special medical which I needed attention, it was
very good, I got this WhatsApp number from
12:30 in the morning on 125th, I was
told what is going to happen now and
from fresh India till 11:30 in the night,
their plane mode setting was on
between the table and accounts and they said that they did not
want the progress of, till 11:30 in the night, the
photo was left here in one place, I had
sent it for the entire process and 1GB has been
sent to me continuously by email to home, I am
in the comment wards, I am getting
so many emails continuously that your
caveat will not be cleared until you will
not be disturbed, now the
responsible image is coming from here, so
reply half-baked, send the photo now,
time knife  From where should I send it to you?
I just said that I do
n't have a Mumbai contact. My voice
officer is leaving me after my appearance. The
phone is not connecting in the admin down there.
So this is a disease of the office deliberately
that you and both the next Amresh had done whatever
money they had raped and gang raped them. They had the
right to do 12 night classes. Those sick people told
them like this and the agency tells you that till you get it
cleared, we will
get you that everything is done. Then I have
not sent that photo. The photo was given to
Deol Hospital. I am ignoring it. I am not sending it.
This is a rogue of Fortis Hospital and my
instant is located in Noida. That is
why it is launched in auditing and addictive and
that day at 11:30, I found any songs from home by
email and stationed someone there.
My photo was of Nehra's quality. I was
searching for it. I happily got it from
Prithvi. You got it verified from behind
and my plane
party was done and I was discharged in the recording.
Even after that people are deleting
Chandni.  Abhinav should keep the people at the square,
then go and tell who does the pose medicine,
they had to go for 12
but I left from there on 1150, wow, then
he also has no peace, there is a drama
going on with us, the watchman is present
at the gate, this drama is going on, they have
played the cash withdrawal section so that they can invest
more money, but I got it, I gave so much money,
but how can I get more money,
personally I was worried about the pimples, I felt bad,
so
because of my son's understanding, with the support of Naina, I got
discharged from the hospital during the exam leave and
then my energy got spoiled, we are talking about
your health insurance, so
what kind of problem is your problem, is the
insurance company
good or is your problem with the hospital,
my device
document is needed on both sides, went to see Amazon and the
report says that it is required from the chapter only, so
where is this rule that
Bhojpuri photo should be sent, I can take it,
and will give it to me, even if I want, I can see how it is,
which two, hold the medium size, not  I don't
have any means, I have a complaint with both of them
that
send me the photo of such an eclipse directed at it,
why can't I give it to me,
why does the hospital need it, these insurance companies do
not understand that they should also set an alarm for crying,
their money can also be lost, the company is
passing the should claim, so
if this is done with simplicity, then
more of their money will be spent on them, either the child's energy,
I try to understand your point a little bit,
you are saying that today was your
discharge day, the day it was your recharge
day,
for a comment, the insurance company is
not printing your printer because of a document and the hospital will
help you in sending the document to the insurance company, so friends, what do you
think was the
intention of the hospital and the insurance company in this happening, this
hospital tension is that it should increase by one more day, so
their inverter, I definitely think that the way the
hospital is troubled,
after the plane passes, this hospital injection
and because of this and generally the energy, this thing which
Generally, in most of the trains, this thing
is seen that on the day of discharge, the
customer has to wait. He had to
wait because he was
in the hospital for four days or five days, two days,
his husband's documentation could have ended at any time,
but today, if a
new one had been taken forward by the Hague, do
you consider the insurance company as a deposit in this,
and how,
why was the form not filled for the first
5 days, why did you also
remember me in the food scam at night at
7:30, that you should fill the form and
put up posters and correct the 10 packs,
why did you not do the unique 12 12:30 earlier,
this is also a very good first that when
6 births are admitted here, then this
documentation should be done first, this
plan should be done first, so from this clash, the
record objective and first set the minimum
that I should have got it passed in the office, whatever was happening, it should be done
exactly like this,
but overall, if seen, you  But your
alarm was set, the only thing is that you had a problem
getting some documentation
that you had to submit on time,
you couldn't edit it on time, so
this is a little loop in our
system, so what message do you want to send about this
problem, to whom do you
want to send this message, and the
message will reach the
hospitals and
insurance companies in English, if it is cashless, then the
day the patient is
admitted to the hospital, it should be released,
brother,
whatever is required,
whatever your friend needs, we should do it in the beginning so that
my hospital and God can provide
employment, the hospital, the insurance
company and below this there is this tension, you think
that they have to extend their day, absolutely, and
somewhere in this you think that the
insurance company is also associated with the hospital,
I am completing the support, so the
owner of the company, why would he
want to lose more money, but the
insurance companies are working Android, you should
understand that the company's
money is going to them and  If all this was serious, would it be the
right thing to do? And the second thing is fenugreek, for the
general public, find this diet so that
you can get admitted to any other place, you
make sure you run, you had decided that by doing this
first, I did not know that I
thought that I would happen like this, and first of all I will
eliminate the depression first, I will talk about it later,
I am very good, but energy, one thing is that this
entire process, although you had
trouble, you had a little trouble on the last day in the next process,
but the
biggest problem was during the emergency of the team,
when he fell ill,
another way of mine, the expenses created, the
insurance company will cover that expense
till the bank, this is a huge facility for you, so this is
a huge facility available in our system,
what message will you send to people about this facility,
what message will you be able to send to people about health insurance,
I say that you have
life insurance or whatever, first of all
you should have medical insurance,
you should click on the college
so that in case of emergency, who was that
Iraqi public Khan who did not give you bread, that
your  I'm going to go ahead and now
my defense should be strong for you
[music]